National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- President's Subject Files, 1968-1988; 2; 12 cubic ft.
  - Central New York Chapter, 1978-1981 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Chapters, 1978-1980 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Conferences, conventions, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Convenor's kit, ca. 1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Cornell University Chapter [Dialogue], 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, incoming--NOW individuals, 1978-1981 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, incoming--non-NOW organizations, 1978-1982 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, outgoing--non-NOW organizations, 1978-1981 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Crises mail, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Do It Now, 1977 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Domestic Relations Law Task Force, 1978-1983 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Dues transmittal forms, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - East End, Chapter [Voices], 1978-1980 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Education Task Force, 1977 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Elections--National NOW, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Employment Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Employment Task Force, 1978-1980 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Human Rights, Division of, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Legislative Gazette, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Legislative issues, 1978-1980 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Legislative package, 1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Lesbian rights, 1978 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Long Island Chapter [Nassau], 1978-1982 (Box 3 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Mailings, 1978-1980 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Membership inquiries, 1978-1980 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Membership lists, 1978-1980 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - National Institute of Education--Curriculum Development, 1977 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - National NOW information, 1977-1981 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - NOW New York State [newsletters], 1977-1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Office space business, 1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Political endorsements, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Reproduction, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Sex discrimination, 1976-1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Task forces, 1977 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Teenage pregnancy, 1977 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Utica chapter, 1978-1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Vouchers paid, 1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Women's Landmark Preservation Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Albany Office, 1979-1981 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Alcoholism, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - American Association of University Women, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Audit Committee Report, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Buffalo Chapter, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - By-laws, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Central New York Chapter, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Chapters, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Chapters, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Child Care Coordinating Council, Inc., 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Concerted Effort, Inc., 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Conference--Resolutions, 1979 June 23-1979 June 24 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, incoming--non NOW individuals, 1979-1981 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, outgoing--National NOW, 1979-1981 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, outgoing--non-NOW individuals, 1979-1981 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, outgoing--NOW individuals, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Crank file, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Family violence, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Feiger, Sheila Molnar, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Feiger, Sheila Molnar, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Finances, 1979-1981 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Grievance, Alpert vs. Larsen, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Legislative packet, 1979 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Lesbian Rights, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Lesbian Rights, 1979-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Lesbian Rights Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Lobby Day, 1979 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Lobbying and legislation, 1979 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Lobbying and legislation, 1979-1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Matrimonial legislation, 1979-1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Middletown Chapter, 1979-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, [Undated] (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - National correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - NOW Material order forms, 1979-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Resolutions, 1979 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Sex discrimination--Varner, Hazel case, 1979 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - State Regional Legislative meetings, 1979 February (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Southern Westchester Chapter, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Workshop information, 1979 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Bylaws, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Chapter development, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Citizen's Party, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Conferences, conventions, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Consciousness Raising Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Elections--NYS NOW, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Feiger, Sheila Molnar, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Greater Syracuse Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Holtzman, Elizabeth--campaign [for District Attorney], 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Human Rights, Division of, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Internal NOW correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Legislative packet, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Lobby Day, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Lobbying and legislation, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Mailing lists, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Matrimonial legislation, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Mohawk Valley Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - National Advisory Council on Women's Educational Programs, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - New York State Nurses Association, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Organization of Women for Legal Awareness, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Organization of Women Ministers, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Political Action Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Political endorsements, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Press releases, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Professional Women in NYS, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Project on the Status and Education of Women, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Rockland County Chapter, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Rockland County Chapter, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Saratoga Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Sex discrimination in education, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - State Council Meeting, 1980 January 12-1980 January 13 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - State Council Meeting, 1980 March 22-1980 March 23 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - State Council Meeting, 1980 May 3-4 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Task forces, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - White House Indepartmental Task Force on Women, 1980 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Ambach, Gordon [Commissioner of Education and President of SUNY], Undated (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Brooklyn Chapter, 1981-1982 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Budget, 1981 (Box 5 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Central New York Chapter, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Chapters, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Conference, 1981 May 15-1981 May 17 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Conference Implementation Committee, 1981; 1983 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Education Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Employment Task Force, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Walk-A-Thon, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Lobby Day, 1981 February 4 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Lobbying, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Mailings, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Marriage and Divorce Task Force, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Marriage and Divorce Task Force--meeting, 1981 March 7 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - New York Women's Sports Association, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Political Action Committee, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Reproductive Rights Task Force, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Rockland County Chapter, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Southern Westchester Chapter, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Task forces, 1981-1982; 1985 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Well Woman Project, 1981 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Convention, 1982 April 2-1982 April 04 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Education, 1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Education, 1982-1983 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Elections, 1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Feminization of poverty, 1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Human Rights, Division of, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Lobby Day, 1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Lobby Day, 1983 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Nassau Chapter, 1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Reproductive rights, 1982 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Reproductive Rights Task Force, 1983 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Subgroup Received, 1990 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Abortion Rights Action--January 18-21--National Vigil for Women's Lives, 1985 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Ad Book, 1985 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Advertising, 1986 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Affirmative Action Bills, 1987 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - American Family Celebration, 1988 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Amicus Briefs: Clubs, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Amicus Briefs: Executive Order 50-AA, 1984-1985 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Amicus Briefs: Liberta--Marital Rape Exemption, 1984 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Amicus Briefs: Marital Records, 1986 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Amicus Briefs: NYS vs Emick (Wife Battering), 1983-1984 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Amicus Briefs: United States Power Squadrons, 1983 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Amicus Briefs: Upper Hudson Valley Planned Parenthood & NYS Department of Health, 1985 (Box 6 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Amsterdam Custody Case, 1986 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Appointments Coalition, 1983 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Appointments Coalition, 1983 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Automation, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Battered Women--Hospital Follow-ups, 1986 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Bork, Robert--Clippings, 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Bork, Robert--Correspondence About, 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Bork, Robert--Literature, 1971; 1978; 1985; 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Bork, Robert--NOW & Coalitions, 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Bork, Robert--Original Mailings, 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Bork, Robert--Study, 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Brawley, Tawana, 1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Brochures (Old), Undated (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Bronx Chapter NOW, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Budget Crisis, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Budget--Treasurer's Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Budget--Treasurer's Reports, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Budgets, 1983-1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Buffalo Chapter NOW, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Caregiving--Testimony on, 1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Central New York Chapter President Peggy L. Murray, 1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Centralized dues collection, 1979; 1981-1982 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Chapter Development, 1980-1981 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Chapter Development, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Chapter Letter, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Chapter Renewal Monetary Report, 1982-1984; 1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Chapter Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Chapters Abroad (Military), 1983 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Child Custody Issues, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Child Custody Speakout, 1984-1986 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Child Support, 1985-1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Civil Rights Abuse Complaint: Esther Shapiro, 1985 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Civil Rights Restoration Act, 1985 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Coalition for Fair Domestic Relations Laws--Lobby Day, 1986 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Coalition of Free Men - Transitions [newsletter], 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Complaints--Individual, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 7 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Department of Education, 1986-1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Discrimination Complaints: Benton, Marie, 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Discrimination Complaints: Bobal, Gail, 1984-1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Discrimination Complaints: Kenna, Laurie, 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Discrimination Complaints: Lavigne, Marianne, 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Discrimination Complaint: Nesbitt, Ellen, 1986 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Discrimination Complaints: Smith, Christine, 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Divorce--Equitable Distribution & Other Financial Issues, 1984-1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Domestic Violence--Diane Pikul, 1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Domestic Violence & Domestic Relations: Proposed Legislation, 1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - ERA, 1984 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - ERA, 1984 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - ERA, 1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - ERA--Discrimination Complaints, 1984-1986 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - ERA--Friedan, Betty, 1986 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - ERA--PAC NOW-NYS, 1984-1987 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - ERA--PAC NOW-NYS, 1984-1987 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - ERA--Vermont, 1986 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Every Woman Coalition, 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Facts on Women 1986 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Federal Executive Order #11246AA, 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Feminization of Power, 1987 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Fundraising, 1980-1983 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Fundraising--Direct Mail, ca. 1980s (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Fundraising Ideas, 1982-1983 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Fundraising--National Fundraising Telephone Solicitation Kit, 1979 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Fundraising--New York City, 1984 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Fundraising--"Pork Roasts", 1984 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Fundraising--President's Phone Solicitation, 1980-1981 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - "Girls Can Do"--Interview Excerpts on Radio London & Radio 1 (Cassette), [1988] (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Goldsmith, Judy--Breakfast (NOW National President), 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Greater Rochester NOW Chapter, 1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Greater Syracuse Chapter, 1987; 1989 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Greater Syracuse Chapter Presidents, Robert Seidenberg and Mary Ann Stone, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Hiring, 1984-1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Holtzman, Liz--Defense, 1987 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Homelessness by Divorce (Women & Children), 1984-1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Insurance, 1984-1988 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Insurance--Background, 1982-1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Insurance--NOW vs Metropolitan Life, 1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Insurance--NOW vs Mutual of Omaha, 1984-1986 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Insurance--NYS Code, 1985-1986 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Insurance & Pension Sex Discrimination, 1983 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Insurance Liability, 1984-1985 (Box 8 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Job Training Partnership Act, 1982-1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Job Training Partnership Act, 1982-1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Job Training Partnership Act, 1982-1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Jobs with Justice, 1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, Judge Anthony, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Kennedy, Judge Anthony, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Labor Law #220, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Legislation, 1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Legislation, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Legislation, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Legislation, 1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Legislation (NYS)--Supported/Opposed by NOW-NYS, 1986 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Legislative Achievements for Women in New York State: A 20-Year Retrospective, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Legislative Program, 1983 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: AIDS, 1986-1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 15)